<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
   <channel>
      <title>Uberflip Help Center Articles - Troubleshoot CTAs</title>
      <link>https://help.uberflip.com/hc/en-us</link>
      <description>Latest articles from Uberflip Help Center</description>
      <language>en-us</language>
      <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 16:05:25 GMT</lastBuildDate>
      <item>
         <title>Embedded CTA brings in on-page apps</title>
         <link>https://help.uberflip.com/hc/en-us/articles/360035297651-Embedded-CTA-brings-in-on-page-apps</link>
         <description><![CDATA[<h2>Issue</h2>
<p>When embedding a CTA outside a Hub (e.g. on a website), the CTA displays unwanted elements from third-party apps installed on the Hub, such as cookie/privacy notices (like OneTrust) or chat widgets (like Drift).</p>
<ul>
<li>Embedded CTA covered by chat</li>
<li>CTA embed hidden behind app</li>
<li>Iframed CTA shows privacy notice</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<h2>Conditions</h2>
<ul>
<li>Hub where the embedded CTA is hosted has third-party script(s) installed which display visual elements, e.g. chat widgets, privacy banners, etc.</li>
<li>
<strong>Where: </strong>CTAs embedded on an external website (not in Hub)</li>
<li>
<strong>Who: </strong>Affects visitors who view the embedded CTA on the non-Hub website</li>
<li>
<strong>When: </strong>Occurs anytime an embedded CTA is displayed on the non-Hub website</li>
<li>Any browser</li>
<li>Any operating system</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<h2>Cause</h2>
<p>When a CTA is embedded into a non-Hub website, it is displayed on that website in an iframe. An iframe simply displays the contents of another website — in this case your Hub. As a result, if the Hub that hosts the embedded CTA also loads any scripts with on-page visual elements (e.g. widgets), those will also be brought into the iframe of the embedded CTA. </p>
<p> </p>
<h2>Steps to Fix</h2>
<p>To resolve this issue, Uberflip needs to add custom code to your Hub that blocks the third-party scripts from being included with your embedded CTAs. For help, please <a href="https://help.uberflip.com/hc/en-us/requests/new">submit a request to our Support team</a>.</p>]]></description>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">360035297651</guid>
         <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 16:08:28 GMT</pubDate>
      </item>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/rssFeed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
   </channel>
</rss>