<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
   <channel>
      <title>Uberflip Help Center Articles - Troubleshoot Hubs</title>
      <link>https://help.uberflip.com/hc/en-us</link>
      <description>Latest articles from Uberflip Help Center</description>
      <language>en-us</language>
      <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 16:05:25 GMT</lastBuildDate>
      <item>
         <title>Can&apos;t find ACS URL for SSO Setup</title>
         <link>https://help.uberflip.com/hc/en-us/articles/360032729372-Can-t-find-ACS-URL-for-SSO-Setup</link>
         <description><![CDATA[<h2>Issue</h2>
<p>I'm trying to set up SSO, but my IdP is asking for an ACS URL, and I can't find it in Uberflip.</p>
<ul>
<li>Can't find ACS URL</li>
<li>Where do I find the Single sign on URL</li>
<li>Problem with SSO setup</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<h2>Conditions</h2>
<ul>
<li>User is trying to set up SSO by uploading Identity Provider Settings using an XML metadata file</li>
<li>User can't export XML metadata file from IdP because of missing ACS URL</li>
<li>User can't find necessary ACS URL in Uberflip</li>
<li>
<strong>Where: </strong>Uberflip SSO Setup (Identity Provider Settings)</li>
<li>
<strong>Who: </strong>Any Primary User with access to the <strong>Security</strong> section under Uberflip Account Settings</li>
<li>
<strong>When: </strong>While trying to configure IdP settings to enable SSO</li>
<li>Any browser</li>
<li>Any operating system</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<h2>Cause</h2>
<p>To set up SSO with Uberflip, you can use an XML metadata file generated by your Identity Provider (IdP). Some IdPs (e.g. Okta) require you to enter an ACS URL (also called a "Single sign on URL" or similar) provided by Uberflip before they will generate this XML file.</p>
<p>The reason the ACS URL is not provided in Uberflip is because it is dynamic: the ACS URL is generated as part of setting up SSO, so it not available <em>before</em> you set up SSO. This leads to a circular situation where you need the XML file to get the ACS URL, but need the ACS URL to get the XML file.</p>
<p> </p>
<h2>Steps to Fix</h2>
<p>Use the following workaround to resolve this issue:</p>
<ol>
<li>In your IdP, go through the process of setting up Uberflip as a new site on which you will use SSO (with SAML).</li>
<li>When you are asked to enter Uberflip's ACS URL, <strong>type in a placeholder value</strong> for now.
<ul>
<li>For example, you can use <code class="no-padding">https://app.uberflip.com/sso/saml2/placeholder</code>
</li>
<li>The real ACS URL will be in the format <code class="no-padding">https://app.uberflip.com/sso/saml2/12345/123456</code>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Complete the setup process and <strong>generate the XML metadata file</strong> in your IdP.</li>
<li>Use the XML metadata file to complete <a href="https://help.uberflip.com/hc/en-us/articles/360020132311" target="_self">the SSO setup process</a> in Uberflip.</li>
<li>Once the SSO setup process is complete, return to <strong>Account Settings &gt; Identity Provider Settings</strong> in Uberflip and click on the <strong>Edit </strong>(pencil) button next to the IdP you just set up.</li>
<li>In the <strong>Edit Identity Provider Settings</strong> screen that appears, make sure you're on the <strong>Basic IdP Settings</strong> tab, then scroll down to the <strong>ACS URL</strong> field and copy the value:<br> <strong><img src="https://help.uberflip.com/hc/article_attachments/360037351231/Security___Identity_Provider___Edit_Settings_-_Uberflip.png" alt="Security___Identity_Provider___Edit_Settings_-_Uberflip.png"></strong>
</li>
<li>Finally, return to your IdP and open the SSO profile you created for Uberflip. Replace the placeholder value you entered earlier with the real ACS URL you copied.<br>
<ul>
<li>In general, you should <strong>not</strong> need to re-generate the XML metadata file.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ol>]]></description>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">360032729372</guid>
         <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 17:33:28 GMT</pubDate>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>Unwanted ads appear on Hub</title>
         <link>https://help.uberflip.com/hc/en-us/articles/360023372611-Unwanted-ads-appear-on-Hub</link>
         <description><![CDATA[<h2>Issue</h2>
<p>Ads are being displayed on a Hub.</p>
<ul>
<li>A "Sponsored Links" section appears near the bottom of the page, like this:<br> <img src="https://help.uberflip.com/hc/article_attachments/360021134691/Uberflip_-_Agent.png" alt="Uberflip_-_Agent.png">
</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<h2>Conditions</h2>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Where:</strong> Item pages</li>
<li>Disqus integration is enabled on affected Hub</li>
<li>User has a basic (free) Disqus account</li>
<li>All browsers</li>
<li>All operating systems</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<h2>Cause</h2>
<p>Ads, in the form of "Sponsored Links", are part of Disqus. If you integrate Disqus with your Hub for comments, and are using a free Disqus account, Disqus will serve ads on any page where Disqus comments appear. These ads can only be disabled on paid Disqus subscriptions.</p>
<p>You can learn more about Disqus advertising settings in <a href="https://help.disqus.com/ads/updating-your-advertising-settings">this article from Disqus</a>.</p>
<p> </p>
<h2>Steps to Fix</h2>
<p>If you want to remove the Disqus ads from your Hub, you have two options:</p>
<ol>
<li>Remove the Disqus integration from your Hub (<strong>Integrations &gt; Disqus &gt; Disconnect</strong>). This option will of course remove all Disqus commenting functionality from the Hub.</li>
<li>Upgrade to a paid Disqus subscription, which enables the ability to remove ads. This option will allow you to retain Disqus commenting functionality on your Hub.</li>
</ol>
<p> </p>]]></description>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">360023372611</guid>
         <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 17:10:24 GMT</pubDate>
      </item>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/rssFeed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
   </channel>
</rss>